Whew!
Ah! Hello! Is it on?
We're live! Yes! It's live!
It's live! Live photos! And live beer!
And three kinds of temples!
So this week, it's Subie again!
Wow! Here it comes!
It's so bad!
Wow! Then, I heard an inarticulate voice...
Oh, my God! Your voice is coming out.
He's screaming!
The power of the royal spider is back!
So... How is everyone doing? It was hot, but there was a lot of lightning yesterday.
Lightning. Are you okay? Are you okay? Lightning. I heard you were struck by lightning.
I didn't get hit. I almost got hit. I almost got hit.
I almost got hit. I was so scared, I almost got hit by a bashin'.
In a situation like this, it's a disadvantage to be tall.
It's always been like this.
That's amazing.
That's where the lightning hits... Boom, boom, boom, boom...
But in the end, it didn't hit.
It didn't hit. That's good, that's good.
Well, well, well, well...
I'm going to continue with the recording, but before that...
But first, I'd like to ask a favor of you live viewers.
Last time I said I'd make a song about Mt.
I asked the audience to send me any pictures they had of Mt.
Fuji, and this time...
There's a mountain in Kanagawa Prefecture called Mt.
Mt. Daisen. It's a pyramid-shaped mountain like this.
It's a cool pyramid-shaped mountain that represents Kanagawa Prefecture.
Yes, I'm thinking of writing a song about Mt.
If you have any good photos of Mt.
If you have any good pictures of Mt. Daisen, please send them to us.
If you have any good pictures of Mt. Daisen, please send them to me.
That's the sound it makes when you send it, right?That's right, that's right, that's the sound you hear when you send a message.
That's what it sounds like when you send a message.
Was it that loud? This way. It's good, right?
It's definitely good.
It's very vigorous. I sent it.
Well, you know... this is short...
I can see it from Syltarma, for example.
Is that right?
So when I see it, I wonder if it's like this or that.
It stands out that much.
It's really triangular, like this.
It's a beautiful triangle.
If you have any pictures, please send them to me.
I'm sure you can see it from the town.
If you have a good view, you can see it.
I can see it, I can see it, I can see it, I can see it, I can see it, I can see it.
Fuji from Tokyo or Yokohama.
Oh, you can see it.
Fuji.
It looks like this.
It's like this.
Like this.
It's like a platform on Mt.
I hope you all enjoy it!
By the way, I'm in a hurry.
Oh, that means...
Now! Immediately!
I'll give you a day or two.
I'd appreciate it if you give me a day or two.
Immediately!
So we're going to start recording.
So, yes, you want to talk about something. Yes, I'd like to have a topic.
I can talk about anything I think.
I don't get any money from the company for transportation.
I've been wanting to go to the water park. You know, the ones that are usually on the ground, very high up and of various kinds.
There are water athletic facilities, you know, on the ground, but they have slides and...There are slides on the water, you know, like that one where you can't fall down, and there's a lot of places like that.
There are slides on the water, and there are things you can do to prevent you from falling down. There are probably a lot of them in various places, but I've been wanting to go there.
Are there any in this area? I think there's one in Shonan, for example.
I've checked it out once myself, and I really want to go.
There's a floating playground on the waterfront.
If you fail on the slide, you'll fall into the water.
It's like the old Showa-era TV shows.
It's nice, isn't it?
By the way... we're having a release event this summer.
Thank you very much.
I hear it's a big deal now. It's selling like hotcakes.
But I'm happy to hear it's number 6 on the daily charts.
We're so happy!
We're at number 666 on the Daily List.
Omen!
What do you think? Well, you know, it's a little awkward to say this, but...
I'd like to go to a night pool.
Like celebrities and their friends. I'd like to go there. It's kind of stylish.
I don't have a western mind, just the desire to be western.
Yes, Shingo and the two backup dancers I'm planning now. The four of us should go together.
Let's go swimming in the night pool. That's not what I meant.
Let's take pictures.
Basically, it's okay to swim, but I'm thinking of a big chair or something.
We can all sit on big chairs and take selfies, drink drinks...
Yes, yes, yes, yes, drinks like this, right?
But I'm famous for swimming there.
No, no, no, it's annoying.
I have to do a lot of swimming!
But now swimming reminds me of swimming... you know, swimmers are really fast, right?
I'm the number one swimmer in Stardust, so I was the number one among all the Starpra idols.
So fast!
But how about swimming? I took swimming lessons once, but I'm not that good...
I can do the 50m in the crowl and the 50m in the dolphin, but that's about it.
But that's about it.
Butterfly is a special technique. Why do I have to swim like that?
You have to learn to swim like that.You can't do it unless you learn it.
You know, when the Olympics come around and Japan wins a medal in the butterfly.
When you go to the pool, you want to do the butterfly.
It's so funny, it's like you're dancing like this, and you can't make any progress at all.
I know exactly what you mean.
It's amazing, isn't it?
I had a swimming pool near my house when I was in high school.
I'm not sure if I can do the backstroke or the butterfly.
I can't do butterfly. I remember when I was in elementary school...
I can't do the butterfly. I can't do the backstroke.
Usually in gym class, there were boys who were fast.
But in the summer, at the swimming pool, there are fast swimmers and other fast swimmers.
There are guys who swim really fast even though their legs are really slow.
I didn't have an image of him, but he's really fast. There's no gap between the two.
Wow, he's kind of cool. He did it!
What about you, Master? I was called the "Flying Fish of Mitaka.
That's old fashioned. It's like right after the war.
Well, I'm no exception. As I've said many times...
There's basically nothing I can't do.
It's not because I love the sport and want to be good at it, but because I want to be popular with women.
I just want to be popular with women. That's the power of activity, isn't it?
That's right. So if I think I'll be popular with women, I'll get involved.
Soccer, skiing, snowboarding...
And because they have a passion to be popular with women, they don't stop until they're popular with women.
But I think most boys are like that.
Of course they want to be a professional baseball player or soccer player, but...
Basically, when a girl says, "Oh, you're so cute," a man's power increases by 1.5 times.
On the other hand, if they don't, I'm not sure I'll be able to do it anytime soon.
I thought I was pretty good at baseball, but when I went to the next tournament, there were a lot of guys who were even better.
I thought I had no choice but to start playing the guitar, but you know, the guitar looks easy when it's played by a pro, or someone who's really good at it.
I thought so too, but my hand was already hurting so much that it started to bleed.
But then someone whispers to me that I'm going to get a lot of attention from the girls at the school festival.
I'm not going to lose... and then the "F" sound came out... I think I'd have quit right away if I hadn't done that.
So it's really important for the girls to cheer for the boys.
A great guy will come out. Good luck, he's so cool!
And here it is, here it is, here it is, here it is, here it is, here it is, here it is, here it is, here it is, here it is, here it is...This, this, this, this, these are the boys who tried to quit something, and now...
To be popular with the Sohbe family, we'll have to keep doing this.
Well, well, well...
First of all...
I'll tell you what day it is today.
This is a personal message from our virtues.
Today is August 18th, Friday, and tomorrow is August 19th.
August 19th.
Yes! Yes, August 19th is the day of "Haiku"!
So, the shortest poem in the world, "Dabune 5-7-5," which was popular in the Edo period (1603-1867), is said to have been written by a famous haiku poet.
Famous haiku poets include
Matsuo Basho's famous haiku "The sound of water diving into an old pond or river
Another famous haiku poet is Matsuo Basho, whose famous haiku, "Old Pond and the Sound of Water Diving into the River," was also popular in the Edo period.
Another famous haiku is by Matsuo Basho, "The sound of water diving into an old pond and river.
We should follow in the footsteps of our great predecessors and think of a quo today.
I'm thinking of thinking of a quo today, following the example of our great predecessors. 575, yes, thank you.
I don't know much about haiku, but it's better to include symbols.
Symbols, words that remind you of the season...
What should I write?
I don't know...
What should I do?
Summer
Ah!
Well, first of all, I...
Okay...
Well, first of all...
I thought it would be good if it was like this.
Yes, yes...
It's a summer sign, isn't it?
Yes.
Because it's summer.
The sound of water plunging into the river...
Hey, hey, hey...
A little bit, a little bit, a little bit...
Half speed
Snap, snap, snap!gaping (esp. mouth)
a little
This is it.
I'll be sued
To Masaoka
To Mr. Masaoka
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Oh! It's made of Sweemin, please!
Please...
This is? I couldn't get a single vote.
It was too early.
Yes, it was early. It was just too late to catch up with the times.
But I understand. It was the first time the sea opened, so everyone was pretty... overjoyed.
Some of them turned it over before going in...
It's good, isn't it? It's great! It's wonderful!
Okay, teacher, let's go for a night swim.
Farewell, everyone! What the heck, it's a little deep.
They were trying to cause trouble in the night pool earlier, and it seems like they're just swimming as fast as they can, and eventually they all go away.
And then they all go away and you end up in a swimming pool. I see... that's good... that's good... that's good.
I'm sure there are a lot of people who are good at haiku who are watching the Devil's Pool right now. I'm sure there are a lot of people who are good at haiku who are watching Devil right now.
I think it's cool, but it's hard to write haiku.
I see... I see...
I've already prepared my haiku.
I'm ready for it.
I'm sure it doesn't matter what it is, does it?
Yes, you can write about how you feel, right?
I'll write about it.
I had a summer's night with a stiff neck and a stiff neck thread.
Good. The guest witch...
That's exactly what I'm talking about.
What's up?
Did you send it?
So soon?
It was a summer night, and I had a frozen neck thread.
And here's the thread. It's very good, it's very good. Can you translate it into modern Japanese?
It's like a very... stiff neck...
Oh, that's it! I'm too stiff. I was right yesterday.That's what I'm talking about! I'm getting a little overzealous. I did it right yesterday.
I was just in Disney Plus... my friend was in it...
I watched the last episode of Star Wars.
Episode 9 I don't remember it at all, so I watched it again... the last episode of Star Wars I'd forgotten.
I watched it again... and it's amazing! What's with the Emperor?
What's with the emperor?
I thought it was a summer night... but there's no symbols in it at all... no symbols at all... but it's great.
There's a lot of stuff here. Let's read it out loud.
Let's read out the last episode of Star Wars.
Wait a minute...
Famienya! Great! This Saturday and Sunday...
I'm waiting. It's going to be great this year, too.
I'll sprinkle water on it. I'll sprinkle water on it.
I'll water it.
I like the plumbing on the shrimp.
I'm glad you're on summer vacation.
Summer vacation, summer vacation, summer vacation.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, it's done.
Did you put it in order again?
Let's read this one too. Spring tour. How was it last week?
I'm listening to you, aren't I?
I'm just asking. You should look like you're putting it all together.
I'm listening to you.
It was great that both of you came last week.
He came, but he didn't make it in time.
Thank you for your hard work on the event.
It was a lot of fun.
You're so cute... my little princess.
Let's all get together this year... and do the Canon Law.
I'll do the Cannon Method with everyone this year...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I couldn't make it to 5.
You have really powerful eyes.
When I look at him and he stares at me like this, I think, "Oh my God!When I looked at him and he was staring at me like this, I thought, "Oh my God.
I didn't mean to stare. I was about to pull out a 50-yen coin.
I was about to pull out a 50-yen coin when he said, "This is all I have on me right now.
Tarantulas are more delicious than pudding.
Insect food, you know...
It's not so much about distribution, but more about communication.
It's not so much distribution, but rather distribution.
Thank you for the hot summer, Sarpongda.
It's refreshing. Not always. No, no, no...
Oh, sometimes it's not refreshing? Is there a time when you're not always fresh?
Now I'm worried. Sometimes it's not refreshing.
Yes, yes, yes, yes. Amazing.
Oh! It's almost over.
Then, do you have any last words?
Can you pick one? There's a lot of entries. We're getting a lot of entries. Wow, we could have a haiku contest.
Or a Haiku contest. It's difficult.
It's hard to think in such a short period of time.
don't think it'll last forever!
I'm a little overwhelmed.
It's the last one. That's for sure.
This time of year, especially around the beginning of August, you think it's going to last forever.
But, it's getting faster and faster.
I don't have time to watch the backward progress from the first game to the fourth game in the morning.
And homework for summer vacation. Can't you just save the games?
There's a lot of it. Good luck.
Thank you very much, everyone. Thank you very much. Let's do it again next time. Yes. It's the Dragon War tournament, isn't it?
Yes, yes, yes. So, I guess we're almost done with the live broadcast, then.
Yes, yes, yes. So I will see you all next week.
See you all next week. See you next week. Thank you very much for all the live broadcasts. Please send us more photos of Mt. Please do.
Next week's live broadcast will start at 7:00 p.m. 7:00 p.m.?
We're going to start early, an hour early, so please come and watch.
7:00 p.m.? Yes, please. Yes, please. See you next week.
See you next week.